# **RO NGOC VO**

## Backend Developer at mgm technology partners Vietnam

DATE OF BIRTH: August 2nd 1996 (23 years old)

EMAIL: - HIDDEN -

PHONE: - HIDDEN -

I'm Ro Ngoc Vo, a junior full stack developer with 1 year of experience in MEAN stack, with good knowledge of Database Design, Design Pattern, Object-Oriented Analysis and Design.

Learning new languages and technologies is what I am passionate about.

I like helping other and work well with group. I can also do some mentoring tasks and code reviewing for other members.

#### SKILL SET

- Node.js: 2 year - Android: 1 year

- MySQL: 2 year

- JavaScript : 2 years

- Java : 1 year

## SKILL SET

Node.js: 2 years Android: 1 year

MySQL: 2 years Javascript: 2 years

Java: 1 year

### WORK EXPERIENCE

mgm technology partners Vietnam

2019 - Present

Backend Developer

1 year

- Developed a TinhTien (tinhtien.org) project
- + TinhTien is an Web-Application that shared expense manager for the activity





- + Technology: Java Spring-Boot, React TypeScript, A12 Widgets(Framework of mgm)
- + Position: React Developer
- Developed a 'Deerberg (deerberg.de)' project
- + Deerberg is an E-commerce store
- + Technology: Java Struts 2, Java Servlet, A12 Widgets(internal framework of mgm), jQuery
- + Position: Junior Fullstack Developer

### Academic Forum of Duy Tan University

Oct 2014 - Present

Administrator

5 years 3 months

- Main responsibilities:
- + Post articles on specialized knowledge as well as life
- + Post editing, offending
- + Managing the forum
- Recognition and Gains:
- + Improve teamwork skill.
- + Improve communication skill, making decision skill.
- + Working in a professional environment.
- + Improve leadership skill

### Duy Tan University

Aug 2018 - Present

Student Researcher

1 year 5 months

- Worked as NodeJS developer
- Developed Facebook Fanpage Management(FFM) Web-Application
- + FFM is a Web-Application that integrated many Facebook Fanpages into one tab browser. Each Fanpage, User can read/reply messages through Web-App, tracking orders, Post/Tracking/Comment on Fanpage's post
- + Position: Backend Developer
- + Technology: NodeJS, SocketIO, MySQL

Freelancer • 2019 - Present

Android Developer

1 year

- Developed a Bitel Commission Management System (BCMS) project
- + BCMS is an android app for agents who can monitor their commission
- + Position: Android developer
- + Technology: Android, Java, Retrofit2, Dagger 2, Lombok, Timber, Gradle, MVP.
- Developed Bitel Ticket Management System (BTMS) project
- + BTMS is an android app that printer ticket for queuer



+ Position: Android developer

+ Technology: Android, Java, Retrofit2, Dagger 2, Lombok, Timber, Gradle, MVP.

Lapurema Holdings • Jun 2018 - Mar 2019

Backend Developer

9 months

- Developed a Zana(https://zanacoin.io) project
- + Zana use innovative functions such as Blockchain and encryption technology to realize cashlessness for everyone who wants to participate in the future life at cryptocurrency)
- + Technology: NodeJS, Angular 6, Firebase
- + Position: Backend Developer(Almost Backend)
- Developed a Human Resource Management (HRM) project
- + A human resource management for Lapurema Holdings
- + Technology: NodeJS, Angular 6, Firebase
- + Position: Backend Developer (Full Backend)
- Developed a Dreamus project
- + A project which likes https://www.kickstarter.com
- + Technology: NodeJS, Angular6, Firebase
- + Position: Backend Developer

### **EDUCATION**

Duy Tan University • 2015 - 2019

Software Engineer Bachelor

Be trained about programming, basic software industry knowledge.

Learn about the integrated system, databases, eCommerce, L.A.M.P system, software architecture, and design, software project management, software process, and quality management, software testing, software measurements, and analysis.

- An Excellent student of 2017-2018
- Got 2nd Prize of Ideahunter 2018.
- Boeing Scholarship of 2016 2017 (GPA 3.75)
- Science research Ranking: Excellent Facebook Fanpage Management(FFM) Project

# Carnegie Mellon University

2018 - 2018

Certification

- Introduction to Software Engineering- Application Development Practices
- Fundamentals of Computing 1- Fundamentals of Computing 2



- Object-Oriented Programming C++ (Advanced Concepts in Computing)
- Introduction to Network & Telecommunications Technology- Requirements Engineering
- Computer Science for Practicing Engineers (Software Construction)
- System Integration Practices- Information System

### **Applications**

- Software Process & Daniel Guality Management
- Software Testing (Verification & Samp; Validation)- Software Measurements & Samp; Analysis

Axon Active Vietnam • 2017 - 2017

Scrum Master

- Understand what Agile and SCRUM means and how it's related to the software project
- Learn how to build high-performance teams

Duy Tan University • 2013 - 2015

Pharmacist Bachelor

Take modules focusing on chemistry, human biology and physiology, pharmaceutics (how medicines are made) and pharmacology (how drugs interact with the body)

- An excellent student of 2014 - 2015

### **LANGUAGES**

English : Proficient

Vietnamese: Native

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Ideahunter 2018 • Oct 2018

Android developer

- 2nd prize.
- Developed Facebook Fanpage Management(FFM)

APEC Economic Leader's Week 2017 • Nov 2017

#### Volunteer

- Main responsibilities:
- + Member of Meeting Team.
- + Reservation a room for members of APEC.
- + Having meeting room decorated before meeting start.



- Recognition and Gains:
- + Improve English skill.
- + Improve communication skill, making decision skill.
- + Working in professional environment.

Scrum Master Course • Jul 2017

Student

Scrum Master Course organized by Axon Active Vietnam

- Recognition and Gains
- + Understand what Agile and SCRUM means and how it's related to the software project
- + Learn how to build high-performance teams

P2A Path To ASIA at Duy Tan University • Jun 2016

Volunteer

- Main responsibilities:

Participated in University exhibition

- Recognition and Gains:

Improve teamwork skill, communication skill

Earth Hour 60+ 2015 • Mar 2015

Team leader of Team 3

- Main responsibilities:
- + Encourage people saving electric power within 1 hour.
- + Riding around Danang City by bicycle
- Recognition and Gains:
- + I can learn teamwork skill, communication skill, leadership skill.
- + Understanding how important of saving energy, clean energy.

Volunteer Club : Hoa Yêu Thương • Jun 2014

Volunteer

From Jun-2018 to the present

Main Activities

- Delivery food to Old/ Disable/ Ethnic minority people
- Fundraising by sell flowers, drink, etc.

